http://www.a1awomensselfdefensesafety.com/privacy

What information do we collect?
We
collect information from you when you register on our site, place an
order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a
form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,
you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may,
however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party
vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART
cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to
your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use
of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network
privacy policy..
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
-To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
-To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
-To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
-To process transactionsYour
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering
the purchased product or service requested.
-To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
-To send periodic emails
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information?
We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal
information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied
sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer
(SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only
accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems,
and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a
transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security
numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information
We use
cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart,
understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of
advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site
interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in
the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist
us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers
are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except
to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you
can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being
sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser
settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our
services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders
by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally,
at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or
services on our website. These third party sites have separate and
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or
liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome
any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please
also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our
website at /terms
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zen desk and save!
Be Sociable, Share!
Tweet
Leave a Reply Cancel reply
You must be logged in to post a comment.
Allow me to introduce myself
like this? Share it!
Recent Posts
Self-Defense-Develop A Strategy For Your Personal Safety And Security
Why the Women’s Self Defense Safety Kit is Your Best Self Defense
Self-Defense – Safety Tips For Personal Protection
MapTestimonial Terrific service! The team is well coordinated; they love their work and very knowledgeable. They have great self defense products! –Cassandra S. Texas.
Self-defense NewsSelf-Defense Force mission in Middle East extended - NHK WORLDSelf-Defense Force mission in Middle East extended  NHK WORLDCommunity invited to artisan fair at Orcutt's Wine Stone Inn on Saturday - Santa Maria TimesCommunity invited to artisan fair at Orcutt's Wine Stone Inn on Saturday  Santa Maria TimesSan Francisco DA’s Office: No Charges Filed In Two Officer-Involved Shootings - CBS San FranciscoSan Francisco DA’s Office: No Charges Filed In Two Officer-Involved Shootings  CBS San FranciscoTestimonial This is a very fashionable website. Everything about the self defense was presented well done and sorted out in a great way. This is my place forever. Julian N.
Resources
About
Babylon
eBay
LA Times
MSN
Tools and Services
Bing
Let Me Hear From You!
